{
    "subject": "resource/Lene_Lai",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Taiwan",
    "human_readable": "Lene Lai was born in Taiwan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9344472885131836,
            "question": "Is Lene Lai from Taiwan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8658031821250916,
            "question": "Where was Lene Lai born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8493205904960632,
            "question": "In which location was Lene Lai born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7812492847442627,
            "question": "Who was born in Taiwan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6758327484130859,
            "question": "What is Lene Lai's country of birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6256375908851624,
            "question": "What country is associated with Lene Lai's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.60709148645401,
            "question": "Taiwan is the birthplace of whom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5915597081184387,
            "question": "Where did Lene Lai originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.549086332321167,
            "question": "Can you tell me Lene Lai's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4163742959499359,
            "question": "Lene Lai hails from which nation?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Lene Lai was born in Taiwan.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8472_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me Lene Lai's birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8472_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Lene Lai originate from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8472_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Taiwan is the birthplace of whom?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8472_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8472_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8472_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8472_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8472_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8472_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8472_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8472_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8472_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8472_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8472_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that Lene Lai was born on 6 June 1989 in Taipei, Taiwan, which supports the statement that she was born in Taiwan."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}